# Ali Kirilov

### Contact

#### **Phone**

+994554764284

#### **Email**

alikirilovz@gmail.com

#### Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kirilov-ali/

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/starkali

#### **Portfolio**

https://starkali.github.io/

## **Computer Skills**

- Linux OS
- Windows Server
- Active Directory
- Microsoft Office
- Advanced Computer System Skills
- Android Studio
- IntelliJ IDEA
- GitHub

# Language

- Russian
- English
- Azerbaijan
- Turkish

# **About Myself**

Determined and devoted IT specialist with a deep interest in programming and networking technologies. My passion for the IT industry drives me to continuously develop and improve in this field. Self-assurance enables me to effectively solve technical challenges and strive for new accomplishments.

## **Work Experience**

### IT Support 2020-2021

Globus Business Center I Baku

#### Network Administrator Assistant 2021-2022

Globus Business Center I Baku

#### Network Administrator 2022-Present

Globus Business Center I Baku

### **Profile**

Proficient in administering Linux and Windows operating systems, system administration, DHCP & DNS, Windows Server, AD DC, GPO, LDAP, file systems, iSCSI, NAS, SAN, vSAN, ESXi, vSphere, VM, and Veeam Backup. Experience with HP & Cisco networking technologies, including VLAN configuration, trunking, LAGG, PoE, Ethernet, Wi-Fi 4/6, IP v4/6.

There is knowledge of Oracle SQL, PL/SQL, MySQL, ERP System, RDBMS, Power BI, Java and web development as well as various other aspects.

## **Education**

### Secondary School 2009-2020

School №186 | Baku

### **Finished Courses And Certificates**

Cisco CyberOps Associate CBROPS 200-201: The Complete Course

Microsoft Power BI

Java and Andriod Development

Oracle PL/SQL Advanced Level Enterprise

**Oracle SQL Certification** 

## **Profession Skills**

Linux Administration, Windows Administration, System Administration, DHCP & DNS Configuration, Windows Server Management, Active Directory (AD) & Domain Controller (DC), Group Policy Objects (GPO), LDAP Integration, File System Management, iSCSI Configuration, Network-Attached Storage (NAS), Storage Area Network (SAN), Virtual SAN (vSAN), VMware ESXi & vSphere, Virtual Machine (VM) Management, Veeam Backup & Recovery, HP Networking Technologies, Cisco Networking Technologies, VLAN Configuration, Trunking, Link Aggregation (LAGG), Power over Ethernet (PoE), Ethernet Technologies, Wi-Fi 4/6 Configuration, IPv4/IPv6 Networking, Oracle SQL, PL/SQL, MySQL, ERP System, Power BI, RDBMS, Java, Web Development.